<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Homework Lesson 6</string>
    <string name="name_field_text">Please enter Your name</string>
    <string name="field1_text">Field 1</string>
    <string name="field2_text">Field 2</string>
    <string name="field3_text">Field 3</string>
    <string name="message_text">PRICE WHEN REVIEWED £199 (32 GB)/£239 (1 32GB) NEXUS 7 TABLET REVIEW (2014) The second-generation Google Nexus 7 has been around for about a year now. The 2013 update of the Nexus 7 is still one of the best 7in Android tablets that money can buy, if not the best. And that is just as well, because the word on the street is that the next smaller Nexus tablet will be a Nexus 8 made by HTC, and that could be curtains for the Asus-built Nexus 7. That would be a travesty, and we retain hopes that the 2013 Nexus 7 will get a little refresh for 2014. In the mean time we\'ve taken the time to refresh our Nexus 7 review. The original Nexus 7 caused quite a stir in the tablet market, primarily due to its low price. This was despite its premium build and specifications, which led many to suspect that Google was subsidising the tablet in order that more people would choose Android and buy more apps, books, music and movies from its digital stores. The updated Nexus 7 went on sale in summer 2013 and was even better in lots of ways than the original. Yes, it cost more, but even in 2014 it remains money well spent, as you’ll see. (See also: The 25 best tablets of 2014: What\'s the best tablet in the UK right now?) NEXUS 7 (2014 REVIEW): DESIGN AND BUILD Design and build is highly unlikely to change. The new Nexus 7 looks very much like the original version but if you’re upgrading from that model then within seconds of taking it out of the box you can tell it\'s next-generation stuff. It\'s slimmer and lighter, measuring just 8.7mm thin and weighing 290g. It\'s marginally taller but far more important are the few millimetres which have been trimmed from the width. It doesn\'t sound like much but the new tablet is significantly easier to hold in one hand. The vast majority of rival 7in tablets, including the Tesco Hudl, Amazon Kindle Fire HD and Advent Vega Tegra Note 7 are all noticeably wider when held upright – enough to make it uncomfortable to stretch your thumb and fingers to grip both sides. Instead, the Nexus 7 is taller and this makes it look rather like an over-sized smartphone. Indeed, the Nexus 7 isn\'t that much bigger than a phablet such as the Nokia Lumia 1520 or Sony Xperia Z Ultra.</string>
</resources>
